change-diapers.com 2019-07-01

# This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Change-Diapers.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://change-diapers.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Change-Diapers.com.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Change-Diapers.com collects, uses, maintains and
discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://change-diapers.com website
("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Change-
Diapers.com.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not
limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in
connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may
be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We
will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to
us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent
them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site.
Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and
technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the
Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their
hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose
to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note
that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Change-Diapers.com collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
         - To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature
           To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to
           them.
         - To send periodic emails
           The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other
           requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that
           may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time
           the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe
           instructions at the bottom of each email.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect
against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username,
password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic
aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding
visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined

above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or
administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your
information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your
permission.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners,
suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links
that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or
from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly
changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies.
Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject
to that website's own terms and policies.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.
These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online
advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your
computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements
that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by
any advertisers.
Google Adsense
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to
Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally
identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email
address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad
and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Changes to this privacy policy
Change-Diapers.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will
revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for
any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.
You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and
become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do
not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be
deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this

site, please contact us at:
Change-Diapers.com
http://change-diapers.com
maria@change-diapers.com
This document was last updated on August 16, 2011
